var DATA_REL_DATE = 1314870172
var CARD_SET_DATA =
[{"id":"4","name":"Tips","description":null,"labels":[],"cards":[{"card_set_id":"4","labels":null,"front":"<b>Formatting</b>","pinyin":null,"back":"<i>, <b>"},{"card_set_id":"4","labels":null,"front":"<b>Good Sites to Practice Worlds</b>","pinyin":null,"back":"techweb.com.cn, tech.sina.com.cn,tech.ifeng.com"}]},{"id":"3","name":"Extras","description":null,"labels":[],"cards":[{"card_set_id":"3","labels":null,"front":"<b>专利</b>","pinyin":null,"back":"patent"},{"card_set_id":"3","labels":null,"front":"<b>下线</b>","pinyin":null,"back":"take offline"},{"card_set_id":"3","labels":null,"front":"<b>博文</b>","pinyin":null,"back":"blog post"},{"card_set_id":"3","labels":null,"front":"<b>CPU的主频</b>\n<small>CPUdezhǔpín</small>","back":"CPU clock speed"},{"card_set_id":"3","labels":null,"front":"<b>电子布告栏</b>\n<small>diànzǐ bùgào</small>","back":"(e) bulletin board"},{"card_set_id":"3","labels":null,"front":"<b>惠普</b>\n<small>huìpǔ</small>","back":"Hewlett Packard"},{"card_set_id":"3","labels":null,"front":"<b>知识产权</b>\n<small>zhīshí chǎnquán</small>","back":"intellectual property"},{"card_set_id":"3","labels":null,"front":"<b>分布式拒绝服务攻击</b>\n<small>fènbù shìjù juéfú wùgōng</small>","back":"denial of service attack"},{"card_set_id":"3","labels":null,"front":"<b>僵尸网络</b>\n<small>jiāngshī wǎngluò</small>","back":"botnet"},{"card_set_id":"3","labels":null,"front":"<b>验证码</b>\n<small>yànzhèngmǎ</small>","back":"verification code (captcha)"},{"card_set_id":"3","labels":null,"front":"<b>宅男,宅女</b>\n<small>zháinán, zháinǚ</small>","back":"nerd,computer(game)addict"},{"card_set_id":"3","labels":null,"front":"<b>休闲游戏</b>\n<small>xiūxián yóuxì</small>","back":"recreational game"},{"card_set_id":"3","labels":null,"front":"<b>摩托罗拉</b>\n<small>mótuō luólā</small>","back":"motorola"},{"card_set_id":"3","labels":null,"front":"<b>应用程序接口</b>\n<small>yīngyòng chéngxù jiēkǒu</small>","back":"API"},{"card_set_id":"3","labels":null,"front":"<b>接线板</b>\n<small>jiēxiànbǎn</small>","back":"power strip"},{"card_set_id":"3","labels":null,"front":"<b>宏达</b>\n<small>hóngdá</small>","back":"HTC"},{"card_set_id":"3","labels":null,"front":"<b>(设备)驱动程序</b>\n<small>(shèbèi)qū dòngchéng</small>","back":"device driver"},{"card_set_id":"3","labels":null,"front":"<b>分区</b>\n<small>fènqū</small>","back":"partition"},{"card_set_id":"3","labels":null,"front":"<b>剪贴半</b>\n<small>jiǎntiēbàn</small>","back":"clipboard"},{"card_set_id":"3","labels":null,"front":"<b>收件人</b>\n<small>shōujiànrén</small>","back":"recipient"},{"card_set_id":"3","labels":null,"front":"<b>视图</b>\n<small>shìtú</small>","back":"View (menu)"},{"card_set_id":"3","labels":null,"front":"<b>上线</b>\n<small>shàngxiàn</small>","back":"go online (live – for a site)"},{"card_set_id":"3","labels":null,"front":"<b>应用程序商店</b>\n<small>yīngyòng chéngxù shāngdiàn</small>","back":"（app store）"},{"card_set_id":"3","labels":null,"front":"<b>字体</b>\n<small>zìtǐ</small>","back":"font"},{"card_set_id":"3","labels":null,"front":"<b>双系统</b>\n<small>shuāngxìtǒng</small>","back":"Dual-boot"},{"card_set_id":"3","labels":null,"front":"<b>水果人者</b>\n<small>shuǐguǒ rénzhě</small>","back":"fruit ninja"},{"card_set_id":"3","labels":null,"front":"<b>网络礼节 </b>\n<small>wǎngluò lǐjiē</small>","back":"netiquette"}]},{"id":"1","name":"Net 250","description":null,"labels":[{"id":"6","name":"email","card_set_id":"1"},{"id":"5","name":"business","card_set_id":"1"},{"id":"4","name":"mobile","card_set_id":"1"},{"id":"3","name":"computer","card_set_id":"1"},{"id":"2","name":"web","card_set_id":"1"},{"id":"1","name":"general","card_set_id":"1"}],"cards":[{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>开发</b>\n<small>kāifā</small>","back":"(software) development"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>设备</b>\n<small>shèbèi</small>","back":"device"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>热点</b>\n<small>rèdiǎn</small>","back":"hotspot"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>虚拟化</b>\n<small>xūnǐhuà</small>","back":"virtualization"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>涂鸦墙</b>\n<small>túyāqiáng</small>","back":"(Facebook) wall"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>宽带</b>\n<small>kuāndài</small>","back":"broadband"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>无线上网卡</b>\n<small>wúxiàn shàngwǎngkǎ</small>","back":"wireless card"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>添加</b>\n<small>tiānjiā</small>","back":"add"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>发送</b>\n<small>fāsòng</small>","back":"send"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>技术支援（支持）</b>\n<small>jìshù zhīyuán （zhīchí）</small>","back":"tech support"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>推特</b>\n<small>tuītè</small>","back":"Twitter"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["4"],"front":"<b>位基服务,移动定位服务，位置服务</b>\n<small>wèijī fúwù, yídòng dìngwèi fúwù ，wèizhì fúwù</small>","back":"LBS"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["3"],"front":"<b>扫描仪</b>\n<small>sǎomiáoyí</small>","back":"scanner"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>用户产生内容,用户生成内容</b>\n<small>yònghù chǎnshēng nèiróng, yònghù shēngchéng nèiróng</small>","back":"User-generated content (UCG)"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>病毒视频</b>\n<small>bìngdú shìpín</small>","back":"viral video"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>网吧</b>\n<small>wǎngba</small>","back":"internet cafe"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>网络论战</b>\n<small>wǎngluò lùnzhàn</small>","back":"flame war"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>制图</b>\n<small>zhìtú</small>","back":"graphics"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>漏洞,错误</b>\n<small>lòudòng, cuòwù</small>","back":"bug"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>备份</b>\n<small>bèifèn</small>","back":"backup"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>触(摸)屏,触感屏幕</b>\n<small>chù(mō)píng, chùgǎn píngmù</small>","back":"Touch-screen"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>极客</b>\n<small>jíkè</small>","back":"geek"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>离线</b>\n<small>líxiàn</small>","back":"offline"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>显示器</b>\n<small>xiǎnshìqì</small>","back":"monitor"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>邀请</b>\n<small>yāoqǐng</small>","back":"invite (v)"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["3"],"front":"<b>个人电脑</b>\n<small>gèrén diànnǎo</small>","back":"PC"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>打印起</b>\n<small>dǎyìnqǐ</small>","back":"printer"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>电信</b>\n<small>diànxìn</small>","back":"telecom"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>数据库</b>\n<small>shùjùkù</small>","back":"database"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>闪存</b>\n<small>shǎncún</small>","back":"flash memory"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>技术</b>\n<small>jìshù</small>","back":"technology"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["3"],"front":"<b>壁纸</b>\n<small>bìzhǐ</small>","back":"wallpaper"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>人肉搜索引擎</b>\n<small>rénròu sōusuǒ yǐnqíng</small>","back":"human flesh search"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>尖端</b>\n<small>jiānduān</small>","back":"cutting edge"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>高科技</b>\n<small>gāokējì</small>","back":"high tech"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["4"],"front":"<b> 蜂窝数据</b>\n<small> fēngwō shùjù</small>","back":"cellular data"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>图标</b>\n<small>túbiāo</small>","back":"icon"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>图片</b>\n<small>túpiàn</small>","back":"image"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>高分辨率</b>\n<small>gāofèn biànlǜ</small>","back":"High-resolution"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>测试</b>\n<small>cèshì</small>","back":"beta (test)"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>火星文</b>\n<small>huǒxīngwén</small>","back":"Martian"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>功能</b>\n<small>gōngnéng</small>","back":"feature,function"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>运行</b>\n<small>yùnxíng</small>","back":"run"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>联系</b>\n<small>liánxì</small>","back":"connect"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>通知</b>\n<small>tōngzhī</small>","back":"alert"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>手势</b>\n<small>shǒushì</small>","back":"gesture"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>截图</b>\n<small>jiétú</small>","back":"screenshot"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>雅虎</b>\n<small>yǎhǔ</small>","back":"yahoo"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>视频会议</b>\n<small>shìpín huìyì</small>","back":"video-conferencing"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>个性化</b>\n<small>gèxìnghuà</small>","back":"customization"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>植物大战僵尸</b>\n<small>zhíwù dàzhàn jiāngshī</small>","back":"Plants vs. Zombies"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>电池</b>\n<small>diànchí</small>","back":"battery"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>黑莓</b>\n<small>hēiméi</small>","back":"blackberry"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>豆瓣</b>","pinyin":null,"back":"douban.com (dòubàn)"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>大众点评网</b>","pinyin":null,"back":"dianping.com (dàzhòng diǎnpíng)"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>简介</b>\n<small>jiǎnjiè</small>","back":"profile"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>网络</b>\n<small>wǎngluò</small>","back":"network"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>窗口</b>\n<small>chuāngkǒu</small>","back":"window"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>推出</b>\n<small>tuīchū</small>","back":"sign out (leave)"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>版本</b>\n<small>bǎnběn</small>","back":"version"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>诺基亚</b>\n<small>nuòjīyà</small>","back":"nokia"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>请求</b>\n<small>qǐngqiú</small>","back":"request"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>推出</b>\n<small>tuīchū</small>","back":"release"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>导航栏</b>\n<small>dǎohánglán</small>","back":"navigation pane"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>兼容</b>\n<small>jiānróng</small>","back":"compatible"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>人人网</b>","pinyin":null,"back":"renren (rénrén)"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>英特尔</b>\n<small>yīngtèěr</small>","back":"intel"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>输入法</b>\n<small>shūrùfǎ</small>","back":"input method"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>电子试算表</b>\n<small>diànzǐ shìsuànbiǎo</small>","back":"spreadsheet"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>程序</b>\n<small>chéngxù</small>","back":"program"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>马云</b>\n<small>mǎyún</small>","back":"Jack Ma"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>菜鸟</b>\n<small>càiniǎo</small>","back":"newbie"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>魔兽世界</b>\n<small>móshòu shìjiè</small>","back":"World of Warcraft"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>开放源码(开源)</b>\n<small>kāifàng yuánmǎ (kāiyuán)</small>","back":"Open-source"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>压缩</b>\n<small>yāsuō</small>","back":"compress"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["6"],"front":"<b>主题</b>\n<small>zhǔtí</small>","back":"subject"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>双核</b>\n<small>shuānghé</small>","back":"Dual-core"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>优酷网</b>\n<small>yōukùwǎng</small>","back":"youku.com"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["4"],"front":"<b>手机</b>\n<small>shǒujī</small>","back":"mobile phone"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>互动</b>\n<small>hùdòng</small>","back":"interactive"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>盖茨</b>\n<small>gàicí</small>","back":"Bill Gates"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>隐私政策, 隐私条例</b>\n<small>yǐnsī zhèngcè, yǐnsī tiáolì</small>","back":"privacy policy"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>网址 （网页地址）</b>\n<small>wǎngzhǐ （wǎngyè dìzhǐ）</small>","back":"URL, site"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>迁移</b>\n<small>qiānyí</small>","back":"migrate"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>芯片</b>\n<small>xīnpiàn</small>","back":"microchip"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>亚马孙</b>\n<small>yàmǎsūn</small>","back":"Amazon"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["4"],"front":"<b>解锁</b>\n<small>jiěsuǒ</small>","back":"unlock"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>接口,界面</b>\n<small>jiēkǒu, jièmiàn</small>","back":"interface"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["3"],"front":"<b>上网本</b>\n<small>shàngwǎngběn</small>","back":"netbook"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["5"],"front":"<b> 愤怒的小鸟</b>\n<small>fènnù de xiǎoniǎo</small>","back":"Angry Birds"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>像素</b>\n<small>xiàngsù</small>","back":"pixel"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>配置</b>\n<small>pèizhì</small>","back":"configuration,settings"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["4"],"front":"<b>安卓</b>\n<small>ānzhuó</small>","back":"android"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>网瘾</b>\n<small>wǎngyǐn</small>","back":"internet addiction"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>报到</b>\n<small>bàodào</small>","back":"Check-in"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>防火长城</b>\n<small>fánghuǒ zhǎngchéng</small>","back":"the great firewall (of china)"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["4"],"front":"<b>运营商</b>\n<small>yùnyíngshāng</small>","back":"operator (phone company)"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>死机</b>\n<small>sǐjī</small>","back":"crash"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>新一代</b>\n<small>xīnyīdài</small>","back":"Next-generation"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>确认</b>\n<small>quèrèn</small>","back":"confirm"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>评论</b>\n<small>pínglùn</small>","back":"comment"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>远程</b>\n<small>yuǎnchéng</small>","back":"remote"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>硅谷</b>\n<small>guīgǔ</small>","back":"silicon valley"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>安装</b>\n<small>ānzhuāng</small>","back":"install"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>黑客</b>\n<small>hēikè</small>","back":"hacker"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>加密</b>\n<small>jiāmì</small>","back":"encryption"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>硬件</b>\n<small>yìngjiàn</small>","back":"hardware"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>关闭</b>\n<small>guānbì</small>","back":"close (window)"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["4"],"front":"<b>越狱</b>\n<small>yuèyù</small>","back":"jailbreak"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>网虫 </b>\n<small>wǎngchóng</small>","back":"internet addict (net work)"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>点击(双击)</b>\n<small>diǎnjī (shuāngjī)</small>","back":"click(double-click)"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>按钮</b>\n<small>ànniǔ</small>","back":"button"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>音频文件</b>\n<small>yīnpín wénjiàn</small>","back":"audio file"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["3"],"front":"<b>光驱</b>\n<small>guāngqū</small>","back":"cd,dvd drive,"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>圈子</b>\n<small>quānzǐ</small>","back":"circle"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>团购网站</b>\n<small>tuángòu wǎngzhàn</small>","back":"group buying"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>工具</b>\n<small>gōngjù</small>","back":"tool"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>平板电脑</b>\n<small>píngbǎn diànnǎo</small>","back":"tablet computer"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>信息</b>\n<small>xìnxī</small>","back":"information"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>社交游戏</b>\n<small>shèjiāo yóuxì</small>","back":"social gaming"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>客户端</b>\n<small>kèhùduān</small>","back":"client (app)"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>平台</b>\n<small>píngtái</small>","back":"platform"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>虚拟商品</b>\n<small>xūnǐ shāngpǐn</small>","back":"virtual good"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>网络游戏</b>\n<small>wǎngluò yóuxì</small>","back":"online gaming"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>三星</b>\n<small>sānxīng</small>","back":"Samsung"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>应用程序</b>\n<small>yīngyòng chéngxù</small>","back":"app"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>视频</b>\n<small>shìpín</small>","back":"video"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>阅读器</b>\n<small>yuèdúqì</small>","back":"E-book reader"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>维基百科</b>\n<small>wéijī bǎikē</small>","back":"wikipedia"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>数字时代</b>\n<small>shùzì shídài</small>","back":"digital age"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>相册</b>\n<small>xiàngcè</small>","back":"album"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["4"],"front":"<b>智能手机</b>\n<small>zhínéng shǒujī</small>","back":"smart phone"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>取消</b>\n<small>qǔxiāo</small>","back":"cancel"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>众包</b>\n<small>zhòngbāo</small>","back":"crowdsourcing"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>聊天室</b>\n<small>liáotiānshì</small>","back":"chat(room)"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>购买车</b>\n<small>gòumǎichē</small>","back":"shopping cart"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>服务器</b>\n<small>fúwùqì</small>","back":"server"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>虚拟专用网</b>\n<small>xūnǐ zhuānyòngwǎng</small>","back":"vpn"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>门户网站</b>\n<small>ménhù wǎngzhàn</small>","back":"portal"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>播客</b>\n<small>bōkè</small>","back":"podcast"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>(网络）论坛</b>\n<small>(wǎngluò）lùntán</small>","back":"discussion forum"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["4"],"front":"<b>移动</b>\n<small>yídòng</small>","back":"mobile"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>社交网络</b>\n<small>shèjiāo wǎngluò</small>","back":"social networking (site)"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>云计算</b>\n<small>yúnjìsuàn</small>","back":"cloud computing"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>域名</b>\n<small>yùmíng</small>","back":"domain name"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>防火墙</b>\n<small>fánghuǒqiáng</small>","back":"firewall"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>电子商务</b>\n<small>diànzǐ shāngwù</small>","back":"E-commerce"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>恶意软件</b>\n<small>èyì ruǎnjiàn</small>","back":"malware"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>木马</b>\n<small>mùmǎ</small>","back":"trojan horse"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>钓鱼</b>\n<small>diàoyú</small>","back":"phishing"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>病毒</b>\n<small>bìngdú</small>","back":"virus"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["6"],"front":"<b>回复</b>\n<small>huífù</small>","back":"reply"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["3"],"front":"<b>桌面</b>\n<small>zhuōmiàn</small>","back":"Desktop (screen)"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>信号</b>\n<small>xìnhào</small>","back":"signal"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>发帖</b>\n<small>fātiē</small>","back":"post"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>同步</b>\n<small>zhèngzài tóngbù</small>","back":"sync"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>摄像头</b>\n<small>shèxiàngtóu</small>","back":"webcam"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["6"],"front":"<b>语音和视频聊天</b>\n<small>yǔyīn hé shìpín liáotiān</small>","back":"voice/video chat"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["6"],"front":"<b>垃圾邮件</b>\n<small>lājī yóujiàn</small>","back":"spam"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["6"],"front":"<b>发(送)</b>\n<small>fā(sòng)</small>","back":"send"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["6"],"front":"<b>已发邮件</b>\n<small>yǐfā yóujiàn</small>","back":"sent mail"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["6"],"front":"<b>标签</b>\n<small>biāoqiān</small>","back":"Label  (tag)"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["6"],"front":"<b>附件</b>\n<small>fùjiàn</small>","back":"attachment"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["6"],"front":"<b>收件箱</b>\n<small>shōujiànxiāng</small>","back":"inbox"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["6"],"front":"<b>转发</b>\n<small>zhuǎnfā</small>","back":"forward"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["6"],"front":"<b>表情符</b>\n<small>biǎoqíngfú</small>","back":"emoticon"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["6"],"front":"<b>草稿</b>\n<small>cǎogǎo</small>","back":"drafts"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["6"],"front":"<b>已删除邮件</b>\n<small>yǐ shānchú yóujiàn</small>","back":"deleted mail"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["6"],"front":"<b>通讯(录)</b>\n<small>tōngxùn(lù)</small>","back":"contact (list), "},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["6"],"front":"<b>归档</b>\n<small>guīdàng</small>","back":"archive"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["6"],"front":"<b>过滤</b>\n<small>guòlǜ</small>","back":"filter (v)"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>土豆网</b>","pinyin":null,"back":"Tudou (tǔdòu)"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>腾讯QQ</b>\n<small>téngxùnQQ</small>","back":"(Tencent) QQ"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>淘宝网</b>","pinyin":null,"back":"taobao (táobǎo)"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>搜狐</b>\n<small>sōuhú</small>","back":"sohu (sōuhú)"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>新浪</b>\n<small>xīnlàng</small>","back":"sina"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>网易</b>\n<small>wǎngyì</small>","back":"netease"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>微软</b>\n<small>wēiruǎn</small>","back":"microsoft"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>谷哥</b>\n<small>gǔgē</small>","back":"google"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>中国移动(通信)</b>\n<small>zhōngguó yídòng (tōngxìn)</small>","back":"china mobile"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>百度</b>\n<small>bǎidù</small>","back":"baidu (bǎidù)"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>苹果(公司)</b>\n<small>píngguǒ (gōngsī)</small>","back":"apple computer"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>应用程序</b>\n<small>yīngyòng chéngxù</small>","back":"apps"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>查看 </b>\n<small>chákàn</small>","back":"view (page) "},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["3"],"front":"<b>笔记本</b>\n<small>bǐjìběn</small>","back":"laptop"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>设置</b>\n<small>shèzhì</small>","back":"settings"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>粘贴</b>\n<small>zhāntiē</small>","back":"paste"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>复制,拷贝</b>\n<small>fùzhì, kǎobèi</small>","back":"copy"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>剪切</b>\n<small>jiǎnqiē</small>","back":"cut"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>编辑,改修</b>\n<small>biānjí, gǎixiū</small>","back":"edit "},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>存储,保存</b>\n<small>cúnchǔ, bǎocún</small>","back":"save"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>登出,注销</b>\n<small>dēngchū, zhùxiāo</small>","back":"logout"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>输入,键入</b>\n<small>shūrù, jiànrù</small>","back":"input"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>删除</b>\n<small>shānchú</small>","back":"delete, remove"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>文件夹</b>\n<small>wénjiànjiá</small>","back":"documents (folder)"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>文件,文档</b>\n<small>wénjiàn, wéndàng</small>","back":"file,document"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>杀毒软件</b>\n<small>shādú ruǎnjiàn</small>","back":"Anti-virus software"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["3"],"front":"<b>硬盘</b>\n<small>yìngpán</small>","back":"hard disk"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>屏幕</b>\n<small>píngmù</small>","back":"screen"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>路由器</b>\n<small>lùyóuqì</small>","back":"router"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["3"],"front":"<b>鼠标</b>\n<small>shǔbiāo</small>","back":"mouse"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["3"],"front":"<b>键盘</b>\n<small>jiànpán</small>","back":"keyboard"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>操作系统</b>\n<small>cāozuò xìtǒng</small>","back":"operating system"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["3"],"front":"<b>电脑</b>\n<small>diànnǎo</small>","back":"computer"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["3"],"front":"<b>内存</b>\n<small>nèicún</small>","back":"memory"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["3"],"front":"<b>(中央)处理器</b>\n<small>(zhōngyāng) chùlǐqì</small>","back":"CPU"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>升级</b>\n<small>shēngjí</small>","back":"upgrade"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>火狐</b>\n<small>huǒhú</small>","back":"firefox"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>状态</b>\n<small>zhuàngtài</small>","back":"status"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>标签页</b>\n<small>biāoqiānyè</small>","back":"tab"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>状态拦</b>\n<small>zhuàngtàilán</small>","back":"status bar"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>历史记录</b>\n<small>lìshǐ jìlù</small>","back":"History  (e.g. browsing history)"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>隐藏</b>\n<small>yǐncáng</small>","back":"hide"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>数据</b>\n<small>shùjù</small>","back":"data"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>表单</b>\n<small>biǎodān</small>","back":"(input) form"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>秘密浏览</b>\n<small>mìmì liúlǎn</small>","back":"private browsing"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>放大,缩小</b>\n<small>fàngdà, suōxiǎo</small>","back":"zoom in, zoom out"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>载入</b>\n<small>zǎirù</small>","back":"load"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>插件</b>\n<small>chājiàn</small>","back":"plug-in"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>导入</b>\n<small>dǎorù</small>","back":"import"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>工具拦</b>\n<small>gōngjùlán</small>","back":"toolbar"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>导出</b>\n<small>dǎochū</small>","back":"export"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>弹出式(广告)</b>\n<small>dànchū shì(guǎnggào)</small>","back":"Pop-up (ad)"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>书签</b>\n<small>shūqiān</small>","back":"bookmark"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>搜索</b>\n<small>sōusuǒ</small>","back":"search"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>无线</b>\n<small>wúxiàn</small>","back":"wireless"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>(超)链接</b>\n<small>(chāo)liànjiē</small>","back":"(hyper)link"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>网上冲浪</b>\n<small>wǎngshàng chōnglàng</small>","back":"web surfer,web surfing"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>密码</b>\n<small>mìmǎ</small>","back":"password"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>用户名</b>\n<small>yònghùmíng</small>","back":"user name"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["4"],"front":"<b>短信</b>\n<small>duǎnxìn</small>","back":"text message"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>上网</b>\n<small>shàngwǎng</small>","back":"(go) online"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>网上交友</b>\n<small>wǎngshàng jiāoyǒu</small>","back":"online dating"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>微博</b>\n<small>wēibó</small>","back":"microblog"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>博客</b>\n<small>bókè</small>","back":"blog"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>网站</b>\n<small>wǎngzhàn</small>","back":"website"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>网友</b>\n<small>wǎngyǒu</small>","back":"net (only) friend"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>登录</b>\n<small>dēnglù</small>","back":"login"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>注册</b>\n<small>zhùcè</small>","back":"register"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>账户</b>\n<small>zhànghù</small>","back":"account"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>下载</b>\n<small>xiàzǎi</small>","back":"download"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>上传</b>\n<small>shàngchuán</small>","back":"upload"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>万维网</b>\n<small>wànwéi wǎng</small>","back":"world wide web"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>网民</b>\n<small>wǎngmín</small>","back":"netizen,internet users"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>首页,主页</b>\n<small>shǒuyè, zhǔyè</small>","back":"home page"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>即时通信</b>\n<small>jíshí tōngxìn</small>","back":"instant messaging"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>在线</b>\n<small>zàixiàn</small>","back":"online"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>(网页）浏览器</b>\n<small>(wǎngyè）liúlǎnqì</small>","back":"(web)browser"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>电子邮件</b>\n<small>diànzǐ yóujiàn</small>","back":"email"},{"card_set_id":"1","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>互联网</b>\n<small>hùliánwǎng</small>","back":"internet"}]},{"id":"2","name":"Net 250 with Examples","description":null,"labels":[{"id":"6","name":"email","card_set_id":"2"},{"id":"5","name":"business","card_set_id":"2"},{"id":"4","name":"mobile","card_set_id":"2"},{"id":"3","name":"computer","card_set_id":"2"},{"id":"2","name":"web","card_set_id":"2"},{"id":"1","name":"general","card_set_id":"2"}],"cards":[{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>开发</b>\n<small>kāifā</small>\n<small><i>谷歌正加速开发Android 4.0</i></small>","back":"<b>(software) development</b>\n<small><i>Google to speed Android 4 development</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>设备</b>\n<small>shèbèi</small>\n<small><i>移动设备</i></small>","back":"<b>device</b>\n<small><i>mobile device</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>热点</b>\n<small>rèdiǎn</small>\n<small><i>将win7电脑无线网变身WiFi热点</i></small>","back":"<b>hotspot</b>\n<small><i>Make Windows 7 wireless machine into a wifi hotspot</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>虚拟化</b>\n<small>xūnǐhuà</small>\n<small><i>使用虚拟化软件，您将可以同时运行 Mac OS X 和 Windows</i></small>","back":"<b>virtualization</b>\n<small><i>Using virtualization software, you can run Mac OSX and Windows at the same time</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>涂鸦墙</b>\n<small>túyāqiáng</small>\n<small><i>Michael 在 Lily 的涂鸦墙上留言:</i></small>","back":"<b>(Facebook) wall</b>\n<small><i>Michael wrote on Lily's wall:</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>宽带</b>\n<small>kuāndài</small>\n<small><i>　实施“宽带中国”战略</i></small>","back":"<b>broadband</b>\n<small><i>implement the “broadband China” strategy</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>无线上网卡</b>\n<small>wúxiàn shàngwǎngkǎ</small>\n<small><i>无线上网卡网速比宽带慢</i></small>","back":"<b>wireless card</b>\n<small><i>A wireless card is slower than broadband</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>添加</b>\n<small>tiānjiā</small>\n<small><i>为此页添加书签</i></small>","back":"<b>add</b>\n<small><i>Bookmark (add bookmark for) this page</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>发送</b>\n<small>fāsòng</small>\n<small><i>用电子邮件发送网页位置</i></small>","back":"<b>send</b>\n<small><i>Send URL by email</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>技术支援（支持）</b>\n<small>jìshù zhīyuán （zhīchí）</small>\n<small><i>微软Windows Xp结束技术支持</i></small>","back":"<b>tech support</b>\n<small><i>Microsoft Windows XP tech support discontinued</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>推特</b>\n<small>tuītè</small>\n<small><i>推特、黑莓是伦敦骚乱主因?</i></small>","back":"<b>Twitter</b>\n<small><i>Were Twitter and Blackberry the causes of the London riots?</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["4"],"front":"<b>位基服务,移动定位服务，位置服务</b>\n<small>wèijī fúwù, yídòng dìngwèi fúwù ，wèizhì fúwù</small>\n<small><i>安卓提供一系列基于位置的服务</i></small>","back":"<b>LBS</b>\n<small><i>Android offers  a series of location-based services</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["3"],"front":"<b>扫描仪</b>\n<small>sǎomiáoyí</small>\n<small><i>用扫描仪把照片扫描进电脑里</i></small>","back":"<b>scanner</b>\n<small><i>use scanner to scan pics to computer</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>用户产生内容,用户生成内容</b>\n<small>yònghù chǎnshēng nèiróng, yònghù shēngchéng nèiróng</small>\n<small><i>youtube依赖于用户产生内容</i></small>","back":"<b>User-generated content (UCG)</b>\n<small><i>Youtube relies on UGC</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>病毒视频</b>\n<small>bìngdú shìpín</small>\n<small><i>最具创意的10大病毒视频</i></small>","back":"<b>viral video</b>\n<small><i>10 most creative viral videos</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>网吧</b>\n<small>wǎngba</small>\n<small><i>很多家长担心孩子去网吧玩游戏</i></small>","back":"<b>internet cafe</b>\n<small><i>Many parents worry about their kids playing games in internet bars</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>网络论战</b>\n<small>wǎngluò lùnzhàn</small>\n<small><i>WOW玩家贬低TERA 引发网络论战</i></small>","back":"<b>flame war</b>\n<small><i>WOW gamers diss Tera, leads to flame war</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>制图</b>\n<small>zhìtú</small>\n<small><i>3D制图</i></small>","back":"<b>graphics</b>\n<small><i>3D graphics</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>漏洞,错误</b>\n<small>lòudòng, cuòwù</small>\n<small><i>Mac OS X系统暴露出的安全性漏洞</i></small>","back":"<b>bug</b>\n<small><i>Mac OSX security bug</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>备份</b>\n<small>bèifèn</small>\n<small><i>数据备份策略</i></small>","back":"<b>backup</b>\n<small><i>data backup strategy</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>触(摸)屏,触感屏幕</b>\n<small>chù(mō)píng, chùgǎn píngmù</small>\n<small><i>总的来说平板电脑有触摸屏</i></small>","back":"<b>Touch-screen</b>\n<small><i>Generally, tablets have touch screens</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>极客</b>\n<small>jíkè</small>\n<small><i>国外极客打造安卓遥控玩具坦克</i></small>","back":"<b>geek</b>\n<small><i>Foreign geeks create Android remote-controlled tank!</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>离线</b>\n<small>líxiàn</small>\n<small><i>离线版本的Google Docs将于今年的推出</i></small>","back":"<b>offline</b>\n<small><i>Google Docs offline version will be released this year</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>显示器</b>\n<small>xiǎnshìqì</small>\n<small><i>液晶显示器</i></small>","back":"<b>monitor</b>\n<small><i>LCD</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>邀请</b>\n<small>yāoqǐng</small>\n<small><i>微软邀请你参加活动</i></small>","back":"<b>invite (v)</b>\n<small><i>Microsoft invites you to participate in event...</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["3"],"front":"<b>个人电脑</b>\n<small>gèrén diànnǎo</small>\n<small><i>IBM个人电脑已经迎来30岁生日</i></small>","back":"<b>PC</b>\n<small><i>The IBM PC has already greeted its 30th birthday</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>打印起</b>\n<small>dǎyìnqǐ</small>\n<small><i>对于打印机用户来说，安装驱动很麻烦</i></small>","back":"<b>printer</b>\n<small><i>Installing drivers is a bother for printer users</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>电信</b>\n<small>diànxìn</small>\n<small><i>中国电信</i></small>","back":"<b>telecom</b>\n<small><i>China Telecom</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>数据库</b>\n<small>shùjùkù</small>\n<small><i>备份和恢复数据库</i></small>","back":"<b>database</b>\n<small><i>backup and restore database</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>闪存</b>\n<small>shǎncún</small>\n<small><i>低价iphone5减少机身闪存依赖icloud服务</i></small>","back":"<b>flash memory</b>\n<small><i>Low-cost iPhone5 relies on iCloud to reduce internal flash memory</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>技术</b>\n<small>jìshù</small>\n<small><i>多媒体技术</i></small>","back":"<b>technology</b>\n<small><i>multimedia technology</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["3"],"front":"<b>壁纸</b>\n<small>bìzhǐ</small>\n<small><i>桌面壁纸</i></small>","back":"<b>wallpaper</b>\n<small><i>desktop wallpaper</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>人肉搜索引擎</b>\n<small>rénròu sōusuǒ yǐnqíng</small>\n<small><i>人肉搜索引擎是指利用人工参与来提纯搜索引擎提供信息</i></small>","back":"<b>human flesh search</b>\n<small><i>Human flesh search means using human labor to clean up search engine results</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>尖端</b>\n<small>jiānduān</small>\n<small><i>尖端科技论坛</i></small>","back":"<b>cutting edge</b>\n<small><i>Cutting-edge tech forum</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>高科技</b>\n<small>gāokējì</small>\n<small><i>最新高科技产品</i></small>","back":"<b>high tech</b>\n<small><i>the latest high tech products</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["4"],"front":"<b> 蜂窝数据</b>\n<small> fēngwō shùjù</small>\n<small><i>iPhone 3G蜂窝数据网怎么设置？</i></small>","back":"<b>cellular data</b>\n<small><i>How to set up iphone 3G data network?</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>图标</b>\n<small>túbiāo</small>\n<small><i>怎么开通和关闭全部QQ图标</i></small>","back":"<b>icon</b>\n<small><i>How to open and close all QQ icons</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>图片</b>\n<small>túpiàn</small>\n<small><i>图片存储为...</i></small>","back":"<b>image</b>\n<small><i>save image as...</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>高分辨率</b>\n<small>gāofèn biànlǜ</small>\n<small><i>高分辨率摄像头</i></small>","back":"<b>High-resolution</b>\n<small><i>High-resolution webcam</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>测试</b>\n<small>cèshì</small>\n<small><i>用户投诉测试版iOS5导致iPhone充电线起火</i></small>","back":"<b>beta (test)</b>\n<small><i>Users complain ios5 beta software causes their power cord to catch fire!</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>火星文</b>\n<small>huǒxīngwén</small>\n<small><i>星文是华人青少年虚构的一种网络语言</i></small>","back":"<b>Martian</b>\n<small><i>Martian is an online language made up by young Chinese</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>功能</b>\n<small>gōngnéng</small>\n<small><i>Firefox 6.0 版新功能</i></small>","back":"<b>feature,function</b>\n<small><i>Firefox 6.0 new features</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>运行</b>\n<small>yùnxíng</small>\n<small><i>Mozilla操作系统将不会运行Android应用</i></small>","back":"<b>run</b>\n<small><i>The Mozilla OS won't run Android apps</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>联系</b>\n<small>liánxì</small>\n<small><i>无法联系服务器</i></small>","back":"<b>connect</b>\n<small><i>unable to connect to server</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>通知</b>\n<small>tōngzhī</small>\n<small><i>好友在线手机通知</i></small>","back":"<b>alert</b>\n<small><i>friend online status alerts</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>手势</b>\n<small>shǒushì</small>\n<small><i>未来iOS手势都会有什么呢</i></small>","back":"<b>gesture</b>\n<small><i>What will future iOS gestures include?</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>截图</b>\n<small>jiétú</small>\n<small><i>截图泄密新一代iPad</i></small>","back":"<b>screenshot</b>\n<small><i>Screenshot leaks next-generation iPad</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>雅虎</b>\n<small>yǎhǔ</small>\n<small><i>必应雅虎搜索市场份额</i></small>","back":"<b>yahoo</b>\n<small><i>BING-Yahoo search market share</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>视频会议</b>\n<small>shìpín huìyì</small>\n<small><i>远程视频会议系统</i></small>","back":"<b>video-conferencing</b>\n<small><i>remote video-conferencing system</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>个性化</b>\n<small>gèxìnghuà</small>\n<small><i>iGoogle 是您个性化的Google 网页</i></small>","back":"<b>customization</b>\n<small><i>iGoogle is your customized Google home page</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>植物大战僵尸</b>\n<small>zhíwù dàzhàn jiāngshī</small>\n<small><i>玩过植物大战僵尸吗？</i></small>","back":"<b>Plants vs. Zombies</b>\n<small><i>Have you played Plants vs. Zombies?</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>电池</b>\n<small>diànchí</small>\n<small><i>充电电池</i></small>","back":"<b>battery</b>\n<small><i>recharge battery</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>黑莓</b>\n<small>hēiméi</small>\n<small><i>RIM拟将QNX操作系统用于黑莓手机</i></small>","back":"<b>blackberry</b>\n<small><i>RIM plans to use its QNX OS in its Blackberry phones</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>豆瓣</b>\n<small><i> 在豆瓣网，有各种不同的爱好小组</i></small>","pinyin":null,"back":"<b>douban.com (dòubàn)</b>\n<small><i>On Douban, there are every sort of common interest groups</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>大众点评网</b>\n<small><i>大众点评网是中国最大的城市生活消费指南网站之一</i></small>","pinyin":null,"back":"<b>dianping.com (dàzhòng diǎnpíng)</b>\n<small><i>Dianping is one of China's largest consumer recommendation sites</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>简介</b>\n<small>jiǎnjiè</small>\n<small><i>编辑简介 </i></small>","back":"<b>profile</b>\n<small><i>edit profile</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>网络</b>\n<small>wǎngluò</small>\n<small><i>网络崩溃</i></small>","back":"<b>network</b>\n<small><i>network crash!</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>窗口</b>\n<small>chuāngkǒu</small>\n<small><i>点击“打开新窗口”</i></small>","back":"<b>window</b>\n<small><i>Click “open new window”</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>推出</b>\n<small>tuīchū</small>\n<small><i>推出聊天</i></small>","back":"<b>sign out (leave)</b>\n<small><i>sign out of chat</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>版本</b>\n<small>bǎnběn</small>\n<small><i>这个应用程序有android版本?</i></small>","back":"<b>version</b>\n<small><i>Does that app have an Android version?</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>诺基亚</b>\n<small>nuòjīyà</small>\n<small><i>苹果超过诺基亚成为第一大手机厂商</i></small>","back":"<b>nokia</b>\n<small><i>Apple surpasses Nokia to become the largest cellphone maker</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>请求</b>\n<small>qǐngqiú</small>\n<small><i>正在发送请求</i></small>","back":"<b>request</b>\n<small><i>Sending request....</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>推出</b>\n<small>tuīchū</small>\n<small><i>2011年6月谷歌推出Google+社交服务</i></small>","back":"<b>release</b>\n<small><i>Google released Google+, its social networking service, in June 2011</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>导航栏</b>\n<small>dǎohánglán</small>\n<small><i>导航栏是网站的“菜单”</i></small>","back":"<b>navigation pane</b>\n<small><i>The navigation pane is a website's “menu”</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>兼容</b>\n<small>jiānróng</small>\n<small><i>微软IE不兼容苹果电脑</i></small>","back":"<b>compatible</b>\n<small><i>Microsoft's IE is not compatible with Macs</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>人人网</b>\n<small><i>人人网是一个中国领先的实名制的社交网络</i></small>","pinyin":null,"back":"<b>renren (rénrén)</b>\n<small><i>Renren is a leading Chinese real-name social network</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>英特尔</b>\n<small>yīngtèěr</small>\n<small><i>英特尔公司是世界上最大的半导体公司</i></small>","back":"<b>intel</b>\n<small><i>Intel is the worlds largest semiconductor maker</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>输入法</b>\n<small>shūrùfǎ</small>\n<small><i>下载谷歌拼音输入法</i></small>","back":"<b>input method</b>\n<small><i>Download Google's pinyin input method (engine)</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>电子试算表</b>\n<small>diànzǐ shìsuànbiǎo</small>\n<small><i>Excel是一款电子试算表的计算机程序</i></small>","back":"<b>spreadsheet</b>\n<small><i>Excel is a spreadsheet program</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>程序</b>\n<small>chéngxù</small>\n<small><i>程序人</i></small>","back":"<b>program</b>\n<small><i>programmer</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>马云</b>\n<small>mǎyún</small>\n<small><i>马云是阿里巴巴集团的创始人</i></small>","back":"<b>Jack Ma</b>\n<small><i>Jack Ma is the founder of Alibaba</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>菜鸟</b>\n<small>càiniǎo</small>\n<small><i>淘宝提醒菜鸟谨防诈骗</i></small>","back":"<b>newbie</b>\n<small><i>Taobao reminds newbies to guard against fraud</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>魔兽世界</b>\n<small>móshòu shìjiè</small>\n<small><i>魔兽世界是一个很热门大型多人在线角色扮演游戏</i></small>","back":"<b>World of Warcraft</b>\n<small><i>World of Warcraft is a very popular MMORPG</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>开放源码(开源)</b>\n<small>kāifàng yuánmǎ (kāiyuán)</small>\n<small><i>Linux是一种操开放源码的作系统</i></small>","back":"<b>Open-source</b>\n<small><i>Linux is an open-source operating system</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>压缩</b>\n<small>yāsuō</small>\n<small><i>7-Zip是一个开放源码的数据压缩程序</i></small>","back":"<b>compress</b>\n<small><i>7-Zip is an open-source data compression program</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["6"],"front":"<b>主题</b>\n<small>zhǔtí</small>\n<small><i>确定要发送没有主题的邮件吗？</i></small>","back":"<b>subject</b>\n<small><i>Please confirm you want to send email without a subject</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>双核</b>\n<small>shuānghé</small>\n<small><i>双核处理器比单核处理器有什么优点?</i></small>","back":"<b>Dual-core</b>\n<small><i>What advantages do dual-core CPU's have over single?</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>优酷网</b>\n<small>yōukùwǎng</small>\n<small><i>优酷是中国最大的视频网站</i></small>","back":"<b>youku.com</b>\n<small><i>Youku is China's largest video site</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["4"],"front":"<b>手机</b>\n<small>shǒujī</small>\n<small><i>我的手机没电了</i></small>","back":"<b>mobile phone</b>\n<small><i>My phone ran out of battery</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>互动</b>\n<small>hùdòng</small>\n<small><i>互动电视</i></small>","back":"<b>interactive</b>\n<small><i>interactive television</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>盖茨</b>\n<small>gàicí</small>\n<small><i>微软的盖茨是全球最有钱人之一</i></small>","back":"<b>Bill Gates</b>\n<small><i>Microsoft's Bill Gates is one of the richest men in the world</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>隐私政策, 隐私条例</b>\n<small>yǐnsī zhèngcè, yǐnsī tiáolì</small>\n<small><i>加拿大将调查Facebook隐私政策</i></small>","back":"<b>privacy policy</b>\n<small><i>Canada will investigate Facebook's privacy policy</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>网址 （网页地址）</b>\n<small>wǎngzhǐ （wǎngyè dìzhǐ）</small>\n<small><i>网址黑名单</i></small>","back":"<b>URL, site</b>\n<small><i>blocked URL list</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>迁移</b>\n<small>qiānyí</small>\n<small><i>从Internet Explorer迁移到Chrome</i></small>","back":"<b>migrate</b>\n<small><i>migrate from Internet Explorer to Chrome</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>芯片</b>\n<small>xīnpiàn</small>\n<small><i>大连英特尔芯片厂成为Intel全球的典范</i></small>","back":"<b>microchip</b>\n<small><i>Dalian chip factory is a model for Intel's worldwide operations</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>亚马孙</b>\n<small>yàmǎsūn</small>\n<small><i>EC2是亚马逊是云服务平台</i></small>","back":"<b>Amazon</b>\n<small><i>EC2 is Amazon's cloud computing platform</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["4"],"front":"<b>解锁</b>\n<small>jiěsuǒ</small>\n<small><i>iPhone 4 解鎖工具釋出</i></small>","back":"<b>unlock</b>\n<small><i>IPhone 4 unlock tool released</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>接口,界面</b>\n<small>jiēkǒu, jièmiàn</small>\n<small><i>图形用户接口</i></small>","back":"<b>interface</b>\n<small><i>graphical user interface</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["3"],"front":"<b>上网本</b>\n<small>shàngwǎngběn</small>\n<small><i>平板电脑热销促使英特尔重新考虑上网本战略</i></small>","back":"<b>netbook</b>\n<small><i>Hot tablet sales have intel rethinking netbook strategy</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["5"],"front":"<b> 愤怒的小鸟</b>\n<small>fènnù de xiǎoniǎo</small>\n<small><i>愤怒的小鸟是最近最为热门的游戏之一</i></small>","back":"<b>Angry Birds</b>\n<small><i>Angry Birds is one of the most popular recent games</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>像素</b>\n<small>xiàngsù</small>\n<small><i>1200万像素手机</i></small>","back":"<b>pixel</b>\n<small><i>1.2 megapixel phone</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>配置</b>\n<small>pèizhì</small>\n<small><i>电脑配置调整</i></small>","back":"<b>configuration,settings</b>\n<small><i>Adjust computer settings</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["4"],"front":"<b>安卓</b>\n<small>ānzhuó</small>\n<small><i>案桌是一种操作系统，主要使用于便携设备</i></small>","back":"<b>android</b>\n<small><i>Android is a年OS mainly used in portable (mobile) devices</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>网瘾</b>\n<small>wǎngyǐn</small>\n<small><i>14岁男孩成功戒除网瘾 举报黑网吧</i></small>","back":"<b>internet addiction</b>\n<small><i>14 year-old boy breaks free from internet addiction!</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>报到</b>\n<small>bàodào</small>\n<small><i>允许用户“报到”是Foursquare的主要特色功能</i></small>","back":"<b>Check-in</b>\n<small><i>Foursquare's main differentiation function is allowing users to “check-in”</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>防火长城</b>\n<small>fánghuǒ zhǎngchéng</small>\n<small><i>很多的外国社交网络占被防火长城封锁</i></small>","back":"<b>the great firewall (of china)</b>\n<small><i>Many foreign social networking sites are blocked by China's great firewall</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["4"],"front":"<b>运营商</b>\n<small>yùnyíngshāng</small>\n<small><i>联通是国内第义家销售iPhone的运营商</i></small>","back":"<b>operator (phone company)</b>\n<small><i>China Unicom is the first domestic operator to offer the iPhone</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>死机</b>\n<small>sǐjī</small>\n<small><i>防止电脑死机的25个提示</i></small>","back":"<b>crash</b>\n<small><i>25 tips to avoid computer crashes</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>新一代</b>\n<small>xīnyīdài</small>\n<small><i>新一代技术</i></small>","back":"<b>Next-generation</b>\n<small><i>Next-generation technology</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>确认</b>\n<small>quèrèn</small>\n<small><i>Ann 在facebook上确认了你是他朋友</i></small>","back":"<b>confirm</b>\n<small><i>Ann confirmed you as a friend</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>评论</b>\n<small>pínglùn</small>\n<small><i>Joe 评论了 jenny 的链接</i></small>","back":"<b>comment</b>\n<small><i>Joe commented on Jenny's link</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>远程</b>\n<small>yuǎnchéng</small>\n<small><i>远程服务器</i></small>","back":"<b>remote</b>\n<small><i>remote server</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>硅谷</b>\n<small>guīgǔ</small>\n<small><i>未来十年中国将诞生硅谷？</i></small>","back":"<b>silicon valley</b>\n<small><i>Can China create a Silicon Valley in the next 10 years?</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>安装</b>\n<small>ānzhuāng</small>\n<small><i>怎么安装最新的电脑杀毒软件？</i></small>","back":"<b>install</b>\n<small><i>How to install the latest anti-virus software?</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>黑客</b>\n<small>hēikè</small>\n<small><i>黑入侵信用卡结算公司的电脑系统</i></small>","back":"<b>hacker</b>\n<small><i>Hackers break into credit card payments company systems</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>加密</b>\n<small>jiāmì</small>\n<small><i>RSA加密算法</i></small>","back":"<b>encryption</b>\n<small><i>RSA encryption algorithm</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>硬件</b>\n<small>yìngjiàn</small>\n<small><i>电脑硬件包括中央处理器,主板等等</i></small>","back":"<b>hardware</b>\n<small><i>computer hardware includes the CPU, motherboard, etc.</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>关闭</b>\n<small>guānbì</small>\n<small><i>自动关闭窗口代码</i></small>","back":"<b>close (window)</b>\n<small><i>Code to automatically close (program) window</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["4"],"front":"<b>越狱</b>\n<small>yuèyù</small>\n<small><i>iPhone Dev Team宣布iPad2越狱成功</i></small>","back":"<b>jailbreak</b>\n<small><i>The iPhone Dev Team announces success jailbreaking iPad2</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>网虫 </b>\n<small>wǎngchóng</small>\n<small><i>超级网虫”连续上网454小时</i></small>","back":"<b>internet addict (net work)</b>\n<small><i>Super internet addict stays online for 454 hours straight!</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>点击(双击)</b>\n<small>diǎnjī (shuāngjī)</small>\n<small><i>鼠标单击变双击问题</i></small>","back":"<b>click(double-click)</b>\n<small><i>Problem where mouse clicks become double-clicks</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>按钮</b>\n<small>ànniǔ</small>\n<small><i>可以点击“Delete”按钮来删除该图片</i></small>","back":"<b>button</b>\n<small><i>You can click the “Delete” button to delete the image</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>音频文件</b>\n<small>yīnpín wénjiàn</small>\n<small><i>音频文件转换器</i></small>","back":"<b>audio file</b>\n<small><i>audio file converter</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["3"],"front":"<b>光驱</b>\n<small>guāngqū</small>\n<small><i>Macbook Air不内置光驱</i></small>","back":"<b>cd,dvd drive,</b>\n<small><i>The MacBook Air doesn't have an internal DVD drive</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>圈子</b>\n<small>quānzǐ</small>\n<small><i>Google+最棒也是最差的功能是圈子</i></small>","back":"<b>circle</b>\n<small><i>The best and worst feature of Google+ is circles</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>团购网站</b>\n<small>tuángòu wǎngzhàn</small>\n<small><i>全美第一大团购网站是Groupon</i></small>","back":"<b>group buying</b>\n<small><i>Groupon is the largest group buying site in the US</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>工具</b>\n<small>gōngjù</small>\n<small><i>应用开发工具</i></small>","back":"<b>tool</b>\n<small><i>application development tool</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>平板电脑</b>\n<small>píngbǎn diànnǎo</small>\n<small><i>平板电脑和笔记本的区别是什么？</i></small>","back":"<b>tablet computer</b>\n<small><i>What's the difference between a tablet computer and a laptop?</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>信息</b>\n<small>xìnxī</small>\n<small><i>信息技术</i></small>","back":"<b>information</b>\n<small><i>information technology</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>社交游戏</b>\n<small>shèjiāo yóuxì</small>\n<small><i>Facebook前四大流行社交游戏Zynga占三席</i></small>","back":"<b>social gaming</b>\n<small><i>Zynga occupies 3 of the 4 places on the top Facebook game (list)</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>客户端</b>\n<small>kèhùduān</small>\n<small><i>手机人人客户端</i></small>","back":"<b>client (app)</b>\n<small><i>Renren mobile client (app)</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>平台</b>\n<small>píngtái</small>\n<small><i>跨平台,多平台</i></small>","back":"<b>platform</b>\n<small><i>Cross-platform, multi-platform</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>虚拟商品</b>\n<small>xūnǐ shāngpǐn</small>\n<small><i>分析称Zynga虚拟商品业务模式毋庸置疑</i></small>","back":"<b>virtual good</b>\n<small><i>Analysts say Zynga's virtual goods business model is for real</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>网络游戏</b>\n<small>wǎngluò yóuxì</small>\n<small><i>最热网络游戏免费下载</i></small>","back":"<b>online gaming</b>\n<small><i>Free download of the hottest online games</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>三星</b>\n<small>sānxīng</small>\n<small><i>三星的案桌智能手机很收欢迎</i></small>","back":"<b>Samsung</b>\n<small><i>Samsung's Android phones are very popular</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>应用程序</b>\n<small>yīngyòng chéngxù</small>\n<small><i>浏览 App Store，你会发现数十万应用程序</i></small>","back":"<b>app</b>\n<small><i>Browse the app store, you can find 100s of thousands of apps</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>视频</b>\n<small>shìpín</small>\n<small><i>视频分享网站</i></small>","back":"<b>video</b>\n<small><i>video sharing site</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>阅读器</b>\n<small>yuèdúqì</small>\n<small><i>传亚马逊很快推下一代Kindle阅读器</i></small>","back":"<b>E-book reader</b>\n<small><i>Amazon will soon release its next generation Kindle reader</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>维基百科</b>\n<small>wéijī bǎikē</small>\n<small><i>维基百科靠志愿者的资金和时间</i></small>","back":"<b>wikipedia</b>\n<small><i>Wikipedia relies on voluteer contributions and time</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>数字时代</b>\n<small>shùzì shídài</small>\n<small><i>数字时代盗版无罪?</i></small>","back":"<b>digital age</b>\n<small><i>Digital age: is piracy a crime?</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>相册</b>\n<small>xiàngcè</small>\n<small><i>Tim在Kunming相册中添加了 4张新照片</i></small>","back":"<b>album</b>\n<small><i>Tim added 4 photos to the album “Kunming”</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["4"],"front":"<b>智能手机</b>\n<small>zhínéng shǒujī</small>\n<small><i>iOS和案桌是最常用的智能手机操作系统</i></small>","back":"<b>smart phone</b>\n<small><i>iOS and Android are the most used smart phone operating systems</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>取消</b>\n<small>qǔxiāo</small>\n<small><i>逆向取消还是确定</i></small>","back":"<b>cancel</b>\n<small><i>Go back, cancel, or confirm?</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>众包</b>\n<small>zhòngbāo</small>\n<small><i>利用众包方式，让社区参与开发产品的过程</i></small>","back":"<b>crowdsourcing</b>\n<small><i>using crowdsurfing to let the community help in the product development process</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>聊天室</b>\n<small>liáotiānshì</small>\n<small><i>交友聊天室</i></small>","back":"<b>chat(room)</b>\n<small><i>chat room to make friends (and find love)</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>购买车</b>\n<small>gòumǎichē</small>\n<small><i>加入购买车</i></small>","back":"<b>shopping cart</b>\n<small><i>add (item) to cart</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>服务器</b>\n<small>fúwùqì</small>\n<small><i>代理服务器</i></small>","back":"<b>server</b>\n<small><i>proxy server</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>虚拟专用网</b>\n<small>xūnǐ zhuānyòngwǎng</small>\n<small><i>虚拟专用网设置，可使用facebook</i></small>","back":"<b>vpn</b>\n<small><i>Set up a VPN and you can use Facebook (in China)</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>门户网站</b>\n<small>ménhù wǎngzhàn</small>\n<small><i>搜狐可能是中国最大的门户网站</i></small>","back":"<b>portal</b>\n<small><i>Sohu may be China's largest internet portal</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>播客</b>\n<small>bōkè</small>\n<small><i>博客与播客的区别是什么？</i></small>","back":"<b>podcast</b>\n<small><i>What's the difference between a blog and podcast?</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>(网络）论坛</b>\n<small>(wǎngluò）lùntán</small>\n<small><i>帮助论坛</i></small>","back":"<b>discussion forum</b>\n<small><i>support forum</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["4"],"front":"<b>移动</b>\n<small>yídòng</small>\n<small><i>移动互联网</i></small>","back":"<b>mobile</b>\n<small><i>mobile internet</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>社交网络</b>\n<small>shèjiāo wǎngluò</small>\n<small><i>人人网是中国的最大的社交网络吗？</i></small>","back":"<b>social networking (site)</b>\n<small><i>Is Renren China's largest social networking site?</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>云计算</b>\n<small>yúnjìsuàn</small>\n<small><i>云计算亚马逊、谷歌、微软三大巨头的战争</i></small>","back":"<b>cloud computing</b>\n<small><i>Cloud computing: Amazon, Google, and Microsoft, war between three giants</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>域名</b>\n<small>yùmíng</small>\n<small><i>域名注册</i></small>","back":"<b>domain name</b>\n<small><i>domain name registration</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>防火墙</b>\n<small>fánghuǒqiáng</small>\n<small><i>黑客新武器：能突破防火墙的鼠标</i></small>","back":"<b>firewall</b>\n<small><i>New hacker weapon: firewall penetrating mouse!</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>电子商务</b>\n<small>diànzǐ shāngwù</small>\n<small><i>截止2011年6月，中国电子商务市场交易额达到2.95万亿</i></small>","back":"<b>E-commerce</b>\n<small><i>China's e-commerce market sales transactions reached $295 billion by June 2011</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>恶意软件</b>\n<small>èyì ruǎnjiàn</small>\n<small><i>报告称Android恶意软件猛增</i></small>","back":"<b>malware</b>\n<small><i>Reports say Android malware increasing rapidly</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>木马</b>\n<small>mùmǎ</small>\n<small><i>黑客用木马来盗取其他用户的个人信息</i></small>","back":"<b>trojan horse</b>\n<small><i>Hackers use Trojan horses to steal personal info</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>钓鱼</b>\n<small>diàoyú</small>\n<small><i>钓鱼是一种企图从电子通信中，获得个人信息的犯罪诈骗过程</i></small>","back":"<b>phishing</b>\n<small><i>Phishing is a attempt to fraudulently get personal info using electronic means</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>病毒</b>\n<small>bìngdú</small>\n<small><i>我的电脑中了病毒,导致系统崩溃.</i></small>","back":"<b>virus</b>\n<small><i>My computer had a virus, which caused system crash</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["6"],"front":"<b>回复</b>\n<small>huífù</small>\n<small><i>你会收到自动回复的邮件</i></small>","back":"<b>reply</b>\n<small><i>You will receive an automatic email reply</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["3"],"front":"<b>桌面</b>\n<small>zhuōmiàn</small>\n<small><i>桌面通知</i></small>","back":"<b>Desktop (screen)</b>\n<small><i>Desktop notifications</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>信号</b>\n<small>xìnhào</small>\n<small><i>手机没信号？换个姿势拿！</i></small>","back":"<b>signal</b>\n<small><i>No phone signal? Change its position</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>发帖</b>\n<small>fātiē</small>\n<small><i>要发帖，需先加入此论坛</i></small>","back":"<b>post</b>\n<small><i>to post you must join this group</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>同步</b>\n<small>zhèngzài tóngbù</small>\n<small><i>正在同步</i></small>","back":"<b>sync</b>\n<small><i>synching...</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>摄像头</b>\n<small>shèxiàngtóu</small>\n<small><i>800万像素摄像头</i></small>","back":"<b>webcam</b>\n<small><i>8 mepapixel webcam</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["6"],"front":"<b>语音和视频聊天</b>\n<small>yǔyīn hé shìpín liáotiān</small>\n<small><i>你用谷歌的语音和视频聊天吗？</i></small>","back":"<b>voice/video chat</b>\n<small><i>Do you use Google's video and voice chat?</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["6"],"front":"<b>垃圾邮件</b>\n<small>lājī yóujiàn</small>\n<small><i>垃圾邮件过滤</i></small>","back":"<b>spam</b>\n<small><i>spam filter</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["6"],"front":"<b>发(送)</b>\n<small>fā(sòng)</small>\n<small><i>我发给她的邮件，都到她的垃圾邮件里面了</i></small>","back":"<b>send</b>\n<small><i>All the emails I sent her ended up in her spam folder</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["6"],"front":"<b>已发邮件</b>\n<small>yǐfā yóujiàn</small>\n<small><i>已发邮件文件夹</i></small>","back":"<b>sent mail</b>\n<small><i>sent mail folder</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["6"],"front":"<b>标签</b>\n<small>biāoqiān</small>\n<small><i>写博客文章时添加标签的一些技巧</i></small>","back":"<b>Label  (tag)</b>\n<small><i>Technique to add tags when writing a blog article</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["6"],"front":"<b>附件</b>\n<small>fùjiàn</small>\n<small><i>包含附件</i></small>","back":"<b>attachment</b>\n<small><i>include attachment</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["6"],"front":"<b>收件箱</b>\n<small>shōujiànxiāng</small>\n<small><i>我的收件箱满了</i></small>","back":"<b>inbox</b>\n<small><i>My inbox is full</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["6"],"front":"<b>转发</b>\n<small>zhuǎnfā</small>\n<small><i>匿名邮件转发服务</i></small>","back":"<b>forward</b>\n<small><i>anonymous email forwarding service</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["6"],"front":"<b>表情符</b>\n<small>biǎoqíngfú</small>\n<small><i>网聊表情符</i></small>","back":"<b>emoticon</b>\n<small><i>chat emoticons</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["6"],"front":"<b>草稿</b>\n<small>cǎogǎo</small>\n<small><i>QQ邮箱里草稿箱的邮件打不开</i></small>","back":"<b>drafts</b>\n<small><i>I can't open the drafts folder in my QQ mailbox</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["6"],"front":"<b>已删除邮件</b>\n<small>yǐ shānchú yóujiàn</small>\n<small><i>为何恢复已删除邮件</i></small>","back":"<b>deleted mail</b>\n<small><i>How to restore deleted mail</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["6"],"front":"<b>通讯(录)</b>\n<small>tōngxùn(lù)</small>\n<small><i>你手机通讯录中有多少人</i></small>","back":"<b>contact (list), </b>\n<small><i>How many people are in your phone's contact list?</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["6"],"front":"<b>归档</b>\n<small>guīdàng</small>\n<small><i>归档邮件</i></small>","back":"<b>archive</b>\n<small><i>archive email</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["6"],"front":"<b>过滤</b>\n<small>guòlǜ</small>\n<small><i>过滤此类邮件</i></small>","back":"<b>filter (v)</b>\n<small><i>filter messages like this</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>土豆网</b>\n<small><i>土豆网是中国的一家大型视频分享网站</i></small>","pinyin":null,"back":"<b>Tudou (tǔdòu)</b>\n<small><i>Tudou is one of China's largest video sharing sites</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>腾讯QQ</b>\n<small>téngxùnQQ</small>\n<small><i>腾讯QQ一款免费即时通信软件</i></small>","back":"<b>(Tencent) QQ</b>\n<small><i>QQ is a free instant messaging software package</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>淘宝网</b>\n<small><i>淘宝网是中国大陆地区最大的购物网站</i></small>","pinyin":null,"back":"<b>taobao (táobǎo)</b>\n<small><i>Taobao.com is China's largest shopping (e-commerce) site</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>搜狐</b>\n<small>sōuhú</small>\n<small><i>搜狐是一家中国大门户占</i></small>","back":"<b>sohu (sōuhú)</b>\n<small><i>Sohu is a large Chinese internet portal</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>新浪</b>\n<small>xīnlàng</small>\n<small><i>新浪微博是全中国最主流,最火爆的微博产品</i></small>","back":"<b>sina</b>\n<small><i>Sina microblog is China's most popular, exciting microblog (product)</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>网易</b>\n<small>wǎngyì</small>\n<small><i>网易是中国领先的互联网技术公司</i></small>","back":"<b>netease</b>\n<small><i>Netease is a leading Chinese internet technology company</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>微软</b>\n<small>wēiruǎn</small>\n<small><i>微软的董事长是比尔·盖茨</i></small>","back":"<b>microsoft</b>\n<small><i>Microsoft's chairman is Bill Gates</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>谷哥</b>\n<small>gǔgē</small>\n<small><i>Google公司致力于互联网搜索</i></small>","back":"<b>google</b>\n<small><i>Google‘s main focus is internet search</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>中国移动(通信)</b>\n<small>zhōngguó yídòng (tōngxìn)</small>\n<small><i>中国移动拥有全球第一的移动通信网络规模</i></small>","back":"<b>china mobile</b>\n<small><i>China mobile has the world's largest communication network</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>百度</b>\n<small>bǎidù</small>\n<small><i>百度是中国网络搜索市场的主导者</i></small>","back":"<b>baidu (bǎidù)</b>\n<small><i>Baidu is the leader in the Chinese search market</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["5"],"front":"<b>苹果(公司)</b>\n<small>píngguǒ (gōngsī)</small>\n<small><i>Steve Jobs是苹果公司的首席运行官</i></small>","back":"<b>apple computer</b>\n<small><i>Steve Jobs is Apple's chairman and CEO</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>应用程序</b>\n<small>yīngyòng chéngxù</small>\n<small><i>苹果App Store应用程序数量超过50万</i></small>","back":"<b>apps</b>\n<small><i>Apple's App Store tops 500,00 apps!</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>查看 </b>\n<small>chákàn</small>\n<small><i>查看 Ann 的个人主页</i></small>","back":"<b>view (page) </b>\n<small><i>view ann's home page</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["3"],"front":"<b>笔记本</b>\n<small>bǐjìběn</small>\n<small><i>笔记本好还是台式电脑好？</i></small>","back":"<b>laptop</b>\n<small><i>Which is better, laptop or desktop?</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>设置</b>\n<small>shèzhì</small>\n<small><i>应用设置</i></small>","back":"<b>settings</b>\n<small><i>apply settings</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>粘贴</b>\n<small>zhāntiē</small>\n<small><i>PDF格式的文件怎么样复制粘贴到Word中</i></small>","back":"<b>paste</b>\n<small><i>How to copy and paste a PDF document into Word</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>复制,拷贝</b>\n<small>fùzhì, kǎobèi</small>\n<small><i>图片直接复制粘贴到桌面</i></small>","back":"<b>copy</b>\n<small><i>copy-paste image directly to desktop</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>剪切</b>\n<small>jiǎnqiē</small>\n<small><i>剪切,粘贴的快捷键分别是什么？</i></small>","back":"<b>cut</b>\n<small><i>what are the cut and paste shortcuts</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>编辑,改修</b>\n<small>biānjí, gǎixiū</small>\n<small><i>不能修改(编辑）只读文件</i></small>","back":"<b>edit </b>\n<small><i>you can't edit a read-only file</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>存储,保存</b>\n<small>cúnchǔ, bǎocún</small>\n<small><i>页面存储为</i></small>","back":"<b>save</b>\n<small><i>save page as...</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>登出,注销</b>\n<small>dēngchū, zhùxiāo</small>\n<small><i>注销账户</i></small>","back":"<b>logout</b>\n<small><i>logout of account</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>输入,键入</b>\n<small>shūrù, jiànrù</small>\n<small><i>请输入你的密码</i></small>","back":"<b>input</b>\n<small><i>please enter your password</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>删除</b>\n<small>shānchú</small>\n<small><i>从朋友中删除</i></small>","back":"<b>delete, remove</b>\n<small><i>delete from friend list</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>文件夹</b>\n<small>wénjiànjiá</small>\n<small><i>压缩一个文件夹</i></small>","back":"<b>documents (folder)</b>\n<small><i>compress (zip) a folder</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>文件,文档</b>\n<small>wénjiàn, wéndàng</small>\n<small><i>文件无法打开</i></small>","back":"<b>file,document</b>\n<small><i>can't open document</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>杀毒软件</b>\n<small>shādú ruǎnjiàn</small>\n<small><i>电脑中毒，无法安装杀毒软件</i></small>","back":"<b>Anti-virus software</b>\n<small><i>computer infected! Can't install anti-virus software!</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["3"],"front":"<b>硬盘</b>\n<small>yìngpán</small>\n<small><i>如何修复硬盘坏道？</i></small>","back":"<b>hard disk</b>\n<small><i>How can a (bad) hard disk be restored?</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>屏幕</b>\n<small>píngmù</small>\n<small><i>屏幕保护</i></small>","back":"<b>screen</b>\n<small><i>Screen-saver</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>路由器</b>\n<small>lùyóuqì</small>\n<small><i>无线路由器</i></small>","back":"<b>router</b>\n<small><i>wireless router</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["3"],"front":"<b>鼠标</b>\n<small>shǔbiāo</small>\n<small><i>你更喜欢用鼠标还是跟踪板</i></small>","back":"<b>mouse</b>\n<small><i>Do you prefer using a mouse or trackpad</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["3"],"front":"<b>键盘</b>\n<small>jiànpán</small>\n<small><i>跑跑游戏、 有专业键盘吗</i></small>","back":"<b>keyboard</b>\n<small><i>Does the Paopao game have a specialized keyboard?</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>操作系统</b>\n<small>cāozuò xìtǒng</small>\n<small><i>谷歌Chrome操作系统或成微软最大威胁</i></small>","back":"<b>operating system</b>\n<small><i>Google Chrome OS could become Microsoft's greatest threat</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["3"],"front":"<b>电脑</b>\n<small>diànnǎo</small>\n<small><i>我的电脑是苹果Macbook</i></small>","back":"<b>computer</b>\n<small><i>My computer is an Apple Macbook</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["3"],"front":"<b>内存</b>\n<small>nèicún</small>\n<small><i>我想把电脑升级到8G内存</i></small>","back":"<b>memory</b>\n<small><i>I want to upgrade my computer to 8 gigs of memory</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["3"],"front":"<b>(中央)处理器</b>\n<small>(zhōngyāng) chùlǐqì</small>\n<small><i>我的笔记本是英特尔2双核处理器</i></small>","back":"<b>CPU</b>\n<small><i>My notebook has an intel dual-core processor</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>升级</b>\n<small>shēngjí</small>\n<small><i>你要升级 电脑</i></small>","back":"<b>upgrade</b>\n<small><i>You need to upgrade your computer</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>火狐</b>\n<small>huǒhú</small>\n<small><i>谷歌工具栏不再支持火狐浏览器</i></small>","back":"<b>firefox</b>\n<small><i>Google toolbar with no longer support Firefox</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>状态</b>\n<small>zhuàngtài</small>\n<small><i>她的在线状态忙碌－别发她IM</i></small>","back":"<b>status</b>\n<small><i>Her online status is busy – don't IM her</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>标签页</b>\n<small>biāoqiānyè</small>\n<small><i>怎么会 打开新标签页</i></small>","back":"<b>tab</b>\n<small><i>How to open a new (browser) tab</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>状态拦</b>\n<small>zhuàngtàilán</small>\n<small><i>显示状态拦</i></small>","back":"<b>status bar</b>\n<small><i>show status bar</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>历史记录</b>\n<small>lìshǐ jìlù</small>\n<small><i>显示所有历史记录</i></small>","back":"<b>History  (e.g. browsing history)</b>\n<small><i>show all history</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>隐藏</b>\n<small>yǐncáng</small>\n<small><i>隐藏窗口</i></small>","back":"<b>hide</b>\n<small><i>hide window</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>数据</b>\n<small>shùjù</small>\n<small><i>清除浏览器数据</i></small>","back":"<b>data</b>\n<small><i>clear browser data</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>表单</b>\n<small>biǎodān</small>\n<small><i>自动填充表单</i></small>","back":"<b>(input) form</b>\n<small><i>AutoFill Form</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>秘密浏览</b>\n<small>mìmì liúlǎn</small>\n<small><i>进行秘密浏览</i></small>","back":"<b>private browsing</b>\n<small><i>Initiate private browsing</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>放大,缩小</b>\n<small>fàngdà, suōxiǎo</small>\n<small><i>图片缩小放大裁切工具</i></small>","back":"<b>zoom in, zoom out</b>\n<small><i>Photo zoom in, out, crop tool</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>载入</b>\n<small>zǎirù</small>\n<small><i>重新载入页面</i></small>","back":"<b>load</b>\n<small><i>reload page</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>插件</b>\n<small>chājiàn</small>\n<small><i>火狐浏览器有很多插件</i></small>","back":"<b>plug-in</b>\n<small><i>Firefox has many plugins</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>导入</b>\n<small>dǎorù</small>\n<small><i>导入文档</i></small>","back":"<b>import</b>\n<small><i>import document</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>工具拦</b>\n<small>gōngjùlán</small>\n<small><i>自定义(定制)工具拦</i></small>","back":"<b>toolbar</b>\n<small><i>Customize toolbar</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>导出</b>\n<small>dǎochū</small>\n<small><i>导出书签</i></small>","back":"<b>export</b>\n<small><i>Export bookmarks</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>弹出式(广告)</b>\n<small>dànchū shì(guǎnggào)</small>\n<small><i>阻止弹出式窗口</i></small>","back":"<b>Pop-up (ad)</b>\n<small><i>Block pop-up windows</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>书签</b>\n<small>shūqiān</small>\n<small><i>为此页添加书签</i></small>","back":"<b>bookmark</b>\n<small><i>Bookmark this page (add bookmark for this page)</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>搜索</b>\n<small>sōusuǒ</small>\n<small><i>google是全世界最大的搜索引擎</i></small>","back":"<b>search</b>\n<small><i>Google is the most popular (largest) search engine in the world</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>无线</b>\n<small>wúxiàn</small>\n<small><i>无线上网卡</i></small>","back":"<b>wireless</b>\n<small><i>wireless internet card</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>(超)链接</b>\n<small>(chāo)liànjiē</small>\n<small><i>超链接打不开</i></small>","back":"<b>(hyper)link</b>\n<small><i>The link doesn't open</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>网上冲浪</b>\n<small>wǎngshàng chōnglàng</small>\n<small><i>中国网民日均网上冲浪2.7小时</i></small>","back":"<b>web surfer,web surfing</b>\n<small><i>Chinese internet users surf on average 2.7 hours per day</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>密码</b>\n<small>mìmǎ</small>\n<small><i>更改密码</i></small>","back":"<b>password</b>\n<small><i>change password</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["1"],"front":"<b>用户名</b>\n<small>yònghùmíng</small>\n<small><i>登录时不显示用户名</i></small>","back":"<b>user name</b>\n<small><i>Don't reveal your user name when you log in</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["4"],"front":"<b>短信</b>\n<small>duǎnxìn</small>\n<small><i>我给你发了那么多条短信,你一条都不回</i></small>","back":"<b>text message</b>\n<small><i>I sent you so many texts, but you didn't send any answer</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>上网</b>\n<small>shàngwǎng</small>\n<small><i>在网吧上网</i></small>","back":"<b>(go) online</b>\n<small><i>go online at an internet cafe</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>网上交友</b>\n<small>wǎngshàng jiāoyǒu</small>\n<small><i>match.com是全球最大的网上交友网站</i></small>","back":"<b>online dating</b>\n<small><i>Match.com is the world's largest dating site</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>微博</b>\n<small>wēibó</small>\n<small><i>Twitter新功能可在用户资料页面发微博</i></small>","back":"<b>microblog</b>\n<small><i>New Twitter feature allows users to microblog to their profile page</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>博客</b>\n<small>bókè</small>\n<small><i>WordPress是一种博客平台</i></small>","back":"<b>blog</b>\n<small><i>WordPress is a blog platform developed in PHP</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>网站</b>\n<small>wǎngzhàn</small>\n<small><i>那个网站打不开</i></small>","back":"<b>website</b>\n<small><i>That website won't open</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>网友</b>\n<small>wǎngyǒu</small>\n<small><i>QQ分组里只显示在线的网友</i></small>","back":"<b>net (only) friend</b>\n<small><i>QQ groups only show online net friends</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>登录</b>\n<small>dēnglù</small>\n<small><i>我忘记了账户密码，无法登录</i></small>","back":"<b>login</b>\n<small><i>I forget my account password and can't log on</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>注册</b>\n<small>zhùcè</small>\n<small><i>新用户注册</i></small>","back":"<b>register</b>\n<small><i>New user registration</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>账户</b>\n<small>zhànghù</small>\n<small><i>其他账户设置我</i></small>","back":"<b>account</b>\n<small><i>other account settings</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>下载</b>\n<small>xiàzǎi</small>\n<small><i>如何在百度下载mp3</i></small>","back":"<b>download</b>\n<small><i>How to download mp3s from Baidu</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>上传</b>\n<small>shàngchuán</small>\n<small><i>我想上传照片到Facebook</i></small>","back":"<b>upload</b>\n<small><i>I want to upload some pics to Facebook</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>万维网</b>\n<small>wànwéi wǎng</small>\n<small><i>浏览万维网</i></small>","back":"<b>world wide web</b>\n<small><i>browse the world wide web</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>网民</b>\n<small>wǎngmín</small>\n<small><i>中国网民数量世界第一</i></small>","back":"<b>netizen,internet users</b>\n<small><i>China has the most internet users in the world</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>首页,主页</b>\n<small>shǒuyè, zhǔyè</small>\n<small><i>首页是打开网站后看到的第一个页面</i></small>","back":"<b>home page</b>\n<small><i>A home page is the first page you see when you visit a site</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>即时通信</b>\n<small>jíshí tōngxìn</small>\n<small><i>即时通信能否取代电子邮件?</i></small>","back":"<b>instant messaging</b>\n<small><i>Can IM replace email?</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>在线</b>\n<small>zàixiàn</small>\n<small><i>我一上QQ看见她在线</i></small>","back":"<b>online</b>\n<small><i>I went on QQ and saw she was online</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>(网页）浏览器</b>\n<small>(wǎngyè）liúlǎnqì</small>\n<small><i>Internet Explorer是微软公司推出的页浏览器</i></small>","back":"<b>(web)browser</b>\n<small><i>Internet Explorer is Microsoft's web browser</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>电子邮件</b>\n<small>diànzǐ yóujiàn</small>\n<small><i>写（电子）邮件</i></small>","back":"<b>email</b>\n<small><i>write (compose) email</i></small>"},{"card_set_id":"2","labels":["2"],"front":"<b>互联网</b>\n<small>hùliánwǎng</small>\n<small><i>互联网是世界上最大的网络</i></small>","back":"<b>internet</b>\n<small><i>The internet is the world's largest network</i></small>"}]}]
